<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Pages on TakoyakiSoft</title><link>https://takoyakisoft.com/en/page/</link><description>Recent content in Pages on TakoyakiSoft</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://takoyakisoft.com/en/page/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Privacy Policy</title><link>https://takoyakisoft.com/en/privacy-policy-app/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://takoyakisoft.com/en/privacy-policy-app/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="handling-of-personal-information">Handling of Personal Information
&lt;/h2>&lt;p>This application provides users with a save data storage function. Save data is stored on the user&amp;rsquo;s device. We will not provide this data to third parties except as required by law.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="advertising">Advertising
&lt;/h2>&lt;p>This application displays advertisements using Google AdMob. AdMob may collect your device&amp;rsquo;s advertising identifier (Advertising ID) and usage data to deliver advertisements tailored to your usage. The collected data is handled in a format that does not identify individuals.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>You can change your ad personalization settings or opt out of data collection through your device&amp;rsquo;s settings menu. For more details, please refer to &lt;a class="link" href="https://support.google.com/admob/answer/6128543" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Google AdMob&amp;rsquo;s Policy&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="data-collection-and-use">Data Collection and Use
&lt;/h2>&lt;p>This application may collect the following data to improve service quality:&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Usage data:&lt;/strong> Frequency of use of functions, etc.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>Collected data is used for analysis in an anonymized state and is not used to identify individuals.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="provision-to-third-parties">Provision to Third Parties
&lt;/h2>&lt;p>The information collected will not be provided to third parties except in the following cases:&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>With the user&amp;rsquo;s consent&lt;/li>
&lt;li>When required by law&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="data-retention-period">Data Retention Period
&lt;/h2>&lt;p>Collected data will be retained for the period necessary to provide the service.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="security">Security
&lt;/h2>&lt;p>We take appropriate security measures to protect the collected data from unauthorized access, loss, falsification, and leakage.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="changes-to-the-privacy-policy">Changes to the Privacy Policy
&lt;/h2>&lt;p>This policy may be revised as necessary. We will notify you in the application of any significant changes.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="contact-us">Contact Us
&lt;/h2>&lt;p>For any questions regarding privacy, please contact us at:
&lt;a class="link" href="../contact/" >Contact Us&lt;/a>&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>About Us</title><link>https://takoyakisoft.com/en/about/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://takoyakisoft.com/en/about/</guid><description>&lt;p>This site provides tutorials on how to use various software. We strive to provide easy-to-understand explanations for beginners, covering topics such as game development with Godot Engine, illustration creation with CLIP STUDIO PAINT, and Windows customization using PowerToys. You can gain a deeper understanding by combining these tutorials with the video content published on &lt;a class="link" href="https://www.youtube.com/@takoyaki-soft" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>TakoyakiSoft&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="about-the-youtube-channel">About the YouTube Channel
&lt;/h2>&lt;p>The &lt;a class="link" href="https://www.youtube.com/@takoyaki-soft" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>TakoyakiSoft&lt;/a> YouTube channel offers video tutorials on how to use various software, including game development with Godot Engine, illustration creation with CLIP STUDIO PAINT, and Windows customization using PowerToys. We upload new videos weekly, so please subscribe!&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="about-the-author">About the Author
&lt;/h2>&lt;p>I will use my experience in programming to explain things in a way that is easy to understand even for beginners, and to help them acquire practical skills.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>My passion for helping others drives my commitment to sharing information. While I&amp;rsquo;ve sometimes offered unsolicited advice in the past, this blog and YouTube channel allow me to connect with those actively seeking the information I provide.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Archives</title><link>https://takoyakisoft.com/en/archives/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://takoyakisoft.com/en/archives/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Contact Us</title><link>https://takoyakisoft.com/en/contact/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://takoyakisoft.com/en/contact/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="contact-form">Contact Form
&lt;/h2>&lt;p>&lt;a class="link" href="https://forms.gle/9xfBqQwDCLACzdCm8" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Google Forms&lt;/a>&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Disclaimer</title><link>https://takoyakisoft.com/en/disclaimer/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://takoyakisoft.com/en/disclaimer/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="accuracy-of-information">Accuracy of Information
&lt;/h2>&lt;p>While we strive to provide accurate and up-to-date information on this website, we make no warranties or representations as to the accuracy, completeness, or usefulness of the content. We will not be liable for any damages or losses arising from actions taken based on the information provided on this site.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="external-links">External Links
&lt;/h2>&lt;p>This website may contain links or banners to other websites. We are not responsible for the information, services, or content provided on these external websites. We shall not be liable for any damages or losses incurred as a result of visiting these linked sites.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="scope-of-disclaimer">Scope of Disclaimer
&lt;/h2>&lt;p>The website operator shall not be liable for any damages incurred by users or third parties in connection with the use of this website. We also reserve the right to modify, delete, or suspend the operation of this website and its content without prior notice.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Privacy Policy</title><link>https://takoyakisoft.com/en/privacy-policy/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://takoyakisoft.com/en/privacy-policy/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="purpose-of-use-of-personal-information">Purpose of Use of Personal Information
&lt;/h2>&lt;p>This website may collect personal information such as your name and email address when you make inquiries. The collected personal information will be used to respond to your inquiries and to contact you via email or other means as necessary. We will not use this information for any other purpose.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="about-advertising">About Advertising
&lt;/h2>&lt;p>This website uses third-party advertising services (Google AdSense). Ad providers may use cookies to display ads relevant to your interests. Cookies can identify your computer, but they cannot identify you personally.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>For information on how to disable cookies and for details regarding Google AdSense, please refer to &amp;ldquo;&lt;a class="link" href="https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Advertising – Policies &amp;amp; Terms – Google&lt;/a>&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="about-access-analysis-tools">About Access Analysis Tools
&lt;/h2>&lt;p>This website uses the following access analysis tools:&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Cloudflare Web Analytics:&lt;/strong> This privacy-focused analytics service does not use cookies, localStorage, or any other client-side state. Traffic data is collected anonymously and does not identify individuals.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Google Analytics:&lt;/strong> This is an access analysis service provided by Google. It uses cookies to collect traffic data. For Google Analytics&amp;rsquo; privacy policy, please refer to &amp;ldquo;&lt;a class="link" href="https://policies.google.com/privacy" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Google Privacy Policy&lt;/a>&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="about-amazon-associates">About Amazon Associates
&lt;/h2>&lt;p>This website participates in the Amazon Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to Amazon.co.jp. When you purchase a product through an Amazon.co.jp link on this site, we receive a referral fee.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Information collected through the Amazon Associates Program does not identify your purchase history or personal information. This website does not access your personal information through the Amazon Associates Program. For Amazon.co.jp&amp;rsquo;s privacy policy, please refer to &amp;ldquo;&lt;a class="link" href="https://www.amazon.co.jp/gp/help/customer/display.html?nodeId=201909010" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Amazon.co.jp Privacy Notice&lt;/a>&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>For any questions or concerns regarding products or services introduced on this site, please contact Amazon.co.jp or the respective vendor.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="about-disqus">About Disqus
&lt;/h2>&lt;p>This website uses Disqus, a third-party service, for its comment function. Disqus may collect user information when comments are posted. Please refer to the &lt;a class="link" href="https://help.disqus.com/en/articles/1717103-disqus-privacy-policy" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Disqus Privacy Policy&lt;/a> for details.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="about-cookies">About Cookies
&lt;/h2>&lt;p>This website uses cookies to enhance user experience and analyze access trends. Cookies are small text files that websites store on your computer. Cookies can identify your computer, but they cannot identify you personally.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>You can refuse the use of cookies by changing your browser settings. However, please note that some features of this website may not function properly if cookies are disabled.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Terms of Service</title><link>https://takoyakisoft.com/en/terms-of-service/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://takoyakisoft.com/en/terms-of-service/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="introduction">Introduction
&lt;/h2>&lt;p>This website (hereinafter referred to as &amp;ldquo;the Website&amp;rdquo;) provides information to explain how to use apps and web services, and to support the acquisition of tools useful for game development. These Terms of Service (hereinafter referred to as &amp;ldquo;the Terms&amp;rdquo;) stipulate the conditions of use of the Website. By using the Website, you are deemed to have agreed to these Terms.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="copyright">Copyright
&lt;/h2>&lt;p>The copyright of the text, images, videos, audio, programs, etc. (hereinafter referred to as &amp;ldquo;Content&amp;rdquo;) published on the Website belongs to the Website operator unless otherwise specified. Reproduction, duplication, sale, publication, or other secondary use of the Content without permission is prohibited, except as permitted by law.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>This Website is not intended to infringe upon copyrights or portrait rights. If you find any problems with the content or images posted on the Website, please contact us via &lt;a class="link" href="../contact/" >Contact Us&lt;/a>. We will respond promptly.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="linking-to-the-website">Linking to the Website
&lt;/h2>&lt;p>In principle, this Website is link-free. Permission or notification is not required to set up a link. However, please note the following points:&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Please clearly indicate that the link is to this Website.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Please refrain from linking in a way that obscures the fact that the content is from this Website, such as displaying the Website&amp;rsquo;s content within a frame.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="prohibited-activities">Prohibited Activities
&lt;/h2>&lt;p>The following activities are prohibited when using this Website:&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Any act that interferes with the operation of the Website&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Any act that causes damage or disadvantage to other users, third parties, or the Website&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Any act that violates public order and morals, or that may violate public order and morals&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Any act that violates laws and regulations or these Terms&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="disclaimer">Disclaimer
&lt;/h2>&lt;p>While we take great care to ensure the accuracy and safety of the Content and information on this Website, we do not guarantee its completeness. We shall not be liable for any damages arising from the use of this Website. Please acknowledge this beforehand.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Search</title><link>https://takoyakisoft.com/en/search/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://takoyakisoft.com/en/search/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Social Media Links</title><link>https://takoyakisoft.com/en/links/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://takoyakisoft.com/en/links/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>